dropshipaccess.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Drop Ship Access

Please take a moment to read the following policy so you understand how we use the personal information we ask you to submit. As we continue to improve our services, this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. If you use any of our services, you agree to these terms.

### Your Privacy

Your privacy is extremely important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices so that you can make informed decisions about the way your information is collected and used. When you register at Drop Ship Access, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to process and communicate with you the status of your orders. We also use your email address to send you newsletters that you may have opted in at the time of registration as well as occasional promotional offers. You can opt out of any newsletters and promotional offers anytime by clicking the "unsubscribe"link at the bottom of the message.

### Information We Collect

We collect the following information when beginning a membership or trial membership: 

  * name
  * billing address
  * phone number
  * email address
  * credit card or debit card information
  * username and password

On some pages, you can order a product and have it drop shipped directly to your customer. In such case, you will need to submit their name and address. We use this information only to ship the order. All of your information and your customer information is kept strictly confidential in accordance with our privacy policy. 

### Data Security

We take every precaution to protect the information of our users.

All sensitive information, such as credit card number, requested during registration is protected by 128 bit SSL encryption technology. While on a secure page the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers becomes locked to indicate that the data being transfered is encrypted.

In addition to using SSL encryption technology, our servers are kept in a secure environment. 

Any questions pertaining to data security can be sent to [support@DropShipAccess.com](mailto:support@DropShipAccess.com).

### Communications

  * Newsletter

Users can opt-out of our newsletter by changing their options in account settings, or by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all emails.

  * Customer service

We communicate regularily with users in order to provide services and assistance at the request of our members.

### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 866 390 5053 or send us an email at [support@DropShipAccess.com](mailto:support@DropShipAccess.com).

Use of the Drop Ship Access services and this website constitutes acceptance of our Membership & Privacy Policy
